# Mert OKAN

İzmir, Turkey



mertokan5020@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mert-okan-522140212

## Summary

I am a graduate in computer programming and I am currently interested in working as a front-end web developer. I have experience in programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript. I am also working on improving my skills in technologies such as React, Next.js, and MongoDB. I have completed one project, a website I made for my friends which can be found at https://www.armaturkbirlikleri.me/. For now, I want to focus on improving my skills in web development. My goal is to develop more advanced web and mobile applications.

## **Experience**

### **Digitalisation**

Cevher Jant Sanayii A.Ş. Oct 2020 - Feb 2021 (5 months)

#### Arge

Cevher Jant Sanayii A.Ş. Sep 2020 - Sep 2020 (1 month)

### **Education**



### Izmir University of Economics

Associate's degree, Computer Programming 2019 - 2021

# Acunmedya Akademi

**Enhanced Software Expertise** Oct 2022 - Jul 2023

## Anadolu University

Licentiate degree, Management Information Systems Sep 2022 - Present

#### Skills

React.js • JavaScript • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML5 • Microsoft SQL Server • C# • Linux